<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Otruth</title>
    <link>https://otruth.org/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Otruth</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 15:45:25 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://otruth.org/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A sneaky attempt to blow €1 million of Obyte funds by Steve Safronoff and Luke Angell</title>
      <link>https://otruth.org/posts/a-sneaky-attempt-to-blow-1-million-euro-of-obyte-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 15:45:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://otruth.org/posts/a-sneaky-attempt-to-blow-1-million-euro-of-obyte-funds/</guid>
      <description>Two people on the Obyte team, Steve Safronoff and Luke Angell, sneakily tried to get their hands on €1 million from the undistributed funds, with a plan anyone could see was awful. They did end up obtaining a large amount, but founder Tony, who controls all the money, refuses to reveal how much he gave them. First a little bit of background on how this happened.
Steve Safronoff hired When Tony publicly launched Obyte at the end of 2016, Steve was not part of the project.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Request to stop abusing Obyte funds (rejected)</title>
      <link>https://otruth.org/posts/request-to-stop-abusing-obyte-funds/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 15:45:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://otruth.org/posts/request-to-stop-abusing-obyte-funds/</guid>
      <description>Background In December 2018 I discovered by chance that Steve Safronoff and Luke Angell had attempted to obtain 1 million Euros from the undistributed Obyte funds. Broadly speaking, they wanted to go travelling around the world with their friends during 2019, paid for using investors money.
By this stage, Steve had already been employed by Obyte as Head of Business Development for 18 months. It was clear to everyone that not only did Steve have absolutely no idea what he was doing, he was also incredibly lazy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Steve Safronoff still does not know who he is supposedly working for</title>
      <link>https://otruth.org/posts/obytes-is-still-called-byteball/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2020 15:45:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://otruth.org/posts/obytes-is-still-called-byteball/</guid>
      <description>Obyte was called Byteball until January 2019. The concept of a name change is not difficult to understand. For Steve Safronoff, though, Head of Business Development, 18 months after the name change he still doesn&amp;rsquo;t even know who he is meant to be working for. In fact using the word work is misleading as Steve avoids doing anything that resembles work. Take a look at his LinkedIn profile as of June 2020:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why this email?</title>
      <link>https://otruth.org/posts/why-this-email/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 May 2020 15:45:25 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://otruth.org/posts/why-this-email/</guid>
      <description>Background to this email The Obyte email newsletter you are receiving started as a voluntary community initiative in January 2018 by me (Paul Murray). Several months later I was contacted by someone on the core Obyte team and offered a paid role, which I accepted. I was part of the core team from April 2018 to March 2020. During my two years there I continued to write the newsletter, and I was in a good position to see what was happening.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>